Caffè Lena collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Subseries 8: ZBS Media collection
    - Sleepy John Estes and Hammie Nixon, June 27, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR432)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0018.
    - Frankie Armstrong (1 of 2), July 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR431)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0017.
    - Frankie Armstrong (2 of 2), July 1974, on 1 side of 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR430)
    - Central Park Sheiks (1 of 2), August 23 or 24, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR434)
    - Central Park Sheiks (2 of 2), August 23 or 24, 1974, on 1 side of 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR435)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0021. Side B is blank.
    - David Amram interview, September 3, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR424)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0010. Side B may be blank.
    - Bill Staines, September 21, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR437)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0023.
    - Michael Cooney, November 4, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR438)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0024.
    - David Amram, accompanied by Charles Chin (guitar), August 3, 1984, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR420)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0006.
    - Pat Webb, on 1 side of 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR417)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0003. Side B is blank.
    - Jacqui and Bridie, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR418)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0004.
    - Coster, Welling and Wallach [Will Welling and Bill Wallach], 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR419)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0005. Coster's first name is not given in the documentation.
    - Dave Van Ronk, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR433)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0019.
    - Happy and Artie Traum, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR436)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0022.
    - Utah Phillips (fill-ups), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR439)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0025.
  - Subseries 9: Jan Nargi collection
    - Music for "You Never Can Tell," 1976 (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR449)
      Copyright 1976 by Mark Cohen.
    - Reynardine, recorded live, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR446)
    - Sweet Land storytellers / Lena's, September 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR458)
    - Sweet Land storytellers / Lena's #2, September 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR459)
    - Short Stories at Sweet Land Weekend [?] / 5 Nasradin [?], 4 Parker, 1 Kawabata / other side un [sic], June 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR450)
    - Paley at Lena's, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR454)
    - Paley at Lena's and Midrash on M [?] / Samuel, W...ts tape 2, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR455)
    - Flame and Frost / 8th Step, December 14, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR466)
    - Caffè - Jeannine, Susan / Letters from my father, October 2, 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR453)
    - Caffè / Intro - Becky, Lois, October 2, 1992, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR456)
    - G. Love and Special Sauce demo tape, 1993, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR469)
    - G. Love and Special Sauce, 1993, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR470)
      Copyright 1993.
    - Caffè Lena S.L. Love Stories Part 2 / Lois - end of W... Blue Star Mountain / Bec - True Love Don Shay (Love and Insectology) / Jeannine - Owls - Louis Nordan [?], February 11, 1995, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR457)
    - Lena / Jeannine and Becky, Part 1, February 4, 1996, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR461)
    - Turnings of the Season - Sweet Land at Lena's / A. Lois - Who Speaks for Wolf / B. Bec - Shrewd Toadie, November 9, 1996, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR460)
    - Sally Harder on WGY, February 27, 1998, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR467)
    - Sally Harder on BBC for Lena's with Richard Dallyn, March 1, 1998, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR468)
    - Sweet Land Caffè Lena #1, December 5, 1998, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR462)
    - Bec Farewell / Caffè Lena, Daughter, Jobs Jobs, Midrash / Stories for Lena's, June 12, 2004, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR451)
    - Pumpkin Freshet Stories Told... at Lena's Sg [?] flies [sic] / A. Bec - Lena's, March 12, 2007, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR465)
    - Jim Scott demo, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR440)
    - Joel Zoss, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR441)
    - Dave and Kay Gordon live, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR442)
      Includes a letter, flyer, and envelope.
    - Rod MacDonald [sampler], 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR443)
      Includes a letter, a flyer, and press clippings.
    - Wicky Sears, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR444)
      Irish traditional music. Includes a small poster.
    - Sound cues for Lena's "Portrayal of Three Women", 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR448)
    - A. Lena's - Mrs. Mowry, Facts of Life, [unclear] / B. Ra... M..., 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR452)
    - Good War: Lena's 1st set (1st and 2nd parts), 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR463)
    - Good War: Lena's 1st set (1st and 2nd parts) (sections), 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR464)
    - [no information], 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR471)
  - Subseries 10: Joe Deuel collection
    - McGarrigles at Caffè Lena, circa 1972, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR508)
    - Paul Geremia (1 of 2), May 27, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR480)
    - Paul Geremia (2 of 2); Peter, Paul and Muffy, May 27, 1989, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR481)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0002. Peter, Paul and Muffy is a folk-comedy trio.
    - Dave Van Ronk (1 of 2), June 17, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR489)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0010.
    - Dave Van Ronk (2 of 2), June 17, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR490)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0011.
    - Paul Geremia, November 11, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR482)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0003. Duplicate recording.
    - Utah Phillips (1 of 2), November 24-25, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR487)
      Last part of the show on November 25 is at end of the November 24 tape. Original item ID: JD B9 0008.
    - Utah Phillips (2 of 2), November 25, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR488)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0009. While other artists are noted, the recording does not include any artists besides Utah.
    - Fred Koller, April 15, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR491)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0012.
    - "Goodbye Ronnie" open mic, January 19, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR492)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0013. "Reagan Night" - artists perform songs revolving around former president Ronald Reagan.
    - Huxtable, Christensen and Hood, June 24, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR493)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0014.
    - Townes Van Zandt (1 of 2), September 24, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR494)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0015. Copy of DK B3 0022, DK B3 0023.
    - Townes Van Zandt (2 of 2), September 24, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR495)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0016. Copy of DK B3 0022, DK B3 0023.
    - Greg Brown (1 of 2; 7 p.m. show), July 21, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR497)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0018.
    - Greg Brown (2 of 2; 10 p.m. show), July 21, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR496)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0017.
    - Roy Bookbinder (1 of 2), November 3, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR499)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0020.
    - Roy Bookbinder (2 of 2), November 3, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR498)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0019.
    - Bucky and John Pizzarelli, 1989, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR500)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0021.
    - Best of Saratoga Springs (ZBS Media), 1989, 2 sound discs (CD): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR503)
      Original item ID: B7 0081. Part of the Caffè Lena History Project collection.
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 1, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR509)
      9 CDs total, donated by John Kribs. From the Caffè Lena History Project collection. Recordings include performances by John Kribs, The Raquette River Rounders, solo show with Arlin Greene on bass, with son Orion on guitar and Doug Moody on fiddle, and Skip Penk. The Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund was founded in 2001.
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 2, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR510)
      See notes for SR509.
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 3, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR511)
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 4, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR512)
      See notes for SR509. Music only; remastered.
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 5, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR513)
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 6, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR514)
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 7, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR515)
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 8, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR516)
    - Southern Adirondacks Musicians Fund benefit concert, CD 9, after 2001, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR517)
    - Racquette River Rounders (1 of 2), August 16, 2002, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR485)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0006.
    - Racquette River Rounders (2 of 2), August 16, 2002, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR486)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0007. Side B is blank.
    - Racquette River Rounders (1 of 2), August 16, 2002, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR483)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0004.
    - Racquette River Rounders (2 of 2), December 27, 2003, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR484)
      Original item ID: JD B9 0005.
    - Caffè Lena Historic Stages, vol. 1, 2004, 1 sound disc (CD): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR504)
      Original item ID: B7 0082. Part of the Caffè Lena History Project collection.
    - Roy Hurd at Caffè Lena (1 of 3), July 15, 2006, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR532)
    - Roy Hurd at Caffè Lena (2 of 3), July 15, 2006, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR533)
    - Roy Hurd at Caffè Lena (3 of 3), July 15, 2006, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR534)
    - Dan Berggsen and Ed Lowman at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), November 18, 2006, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR535)
    - Dan Berggsen and Ed Lowman at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), November 18, 2006, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR536)
    - Roy Hurd at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), June 30, 2008, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR537)
    - Roy Hurd at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), June 30, 2008, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR538)
    - Roy Hurd at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), July, 2009, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR539)
    - Roy Hurd at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), July, 2009, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR540)
    - Dan Berggsen and John Kirk at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), November 15, 2009, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR541)
    - Dan Berggsen and John Kirk at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), November 15, 2009, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR542)
    - Jamcrackers (1 of 2), August 2010, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR543)
    - Jamcrackers (2 of 2), August 2010, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR544)
    - John Kribs at Caffè Lena (house mix), October 22, 2010, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR546)
    - John Kribs at Caffè Lena (room mix), October 22, 2010, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR547)
    - John Kribs at Caffè Lena, October 22, 2010, 1 sound disc (CD-R; 00:02:46): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR547)
      One track only: Kribs tells a story about Lena Spencer, in tribute to her.
    - North Country Friends, December 3, 2010, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR545)
    - Holly and Evan: Acoustic Blues of the Capital Region, 2010, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR502)
      Donated by Kathy Conway. From the Caffè Lena History Project collection.
    - Bob Dylan 70th birthday tribute and Caffè Lena 51st anniversary concert (1 of 2), May 21, 2011, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR549)
      Benefit and celebration held at Skidmore College Dance Theater, Saratoga Springs, NY. 13 tracks.
    - Bob Dylan 70th birthday tribute and Caffè Lena 51st anniversary concert (2 of 2), May 21, 2011, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR550)
      Benefit and celebration held at Skidmore College Dance Theater, Saratoga Springs, NY. 15 tracks.
    - Caffè Lena History Project, CD 1, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR505)
      Selections from four performances at Caffè Lena.
      - Eddy Lawrence, March 28, 1992
      - Cheryl Wheeler, March 28, 1992
      - Cheryl Wheeler, March 20, 1993
      - Camille West, March 4, 1994
    - Caffè Lena History Project, CD 2, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR506)
      - Patty Larkin, November 8, 1992
      - Livingston Taylor, March 6, 1993
      - Kristen Hall, March 13, 1994
      - Livingston Taylor, April 16, 1994
    - Caffè Lena History Project, CD 3, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR507)
      - Rory Block, November 13, 1993
- Series 3: Graphic Materials
  - Subseries 1: Caffè Lena: older history and activities, 1970s-2000s, undated
    - Caffè Lena: history (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Caffè Lena: capital campaign (Box-folder 21/2)
      Two black and white positives of advertisement for the campaign.
    - The Hostage (Caffè Lena Theatre), 1978 (Box-folder 21/3)
      Play staged at Caffè Lena Theatre; color photos both of the production and off-stage activities.
    - Caffè Lena building: interior and exterior (set 1) (Box-folder 21/4)
      Interior and exterior of the building. Color images, captioned.
    - Caffè Lena building: interior and exterior (set 2) (Box-folder 21/5)
      See note for the first set of building images.
    - Folk-A-Thon, 1998 (Box-folder 21/6)
      Color photos; most are of performers on the Caffè Lena stage.
    - Arlo Guthrie at a post-performance reception (Box-folder 21/7)
      Several duplicate copies; all photos are in color.
    - Performers (Box-folder 21/8)
      Most photos are black and white; a few are in color.
    - Caffè Lena from the air (Box-folder 21/9)
      Color photo of Caffè Lena and the surrounding neighborhood, photographed from the air.
    - Model and diagrams of Caffè Lena building (Box-folder 21/10)
      Color photos, showing both interior and exterior views.
    - Lena Spencer, circa 1970s (Box-folder 21/11)
      Lena photographed in the kitchen, plus other informal photos, and also in a stage play.
    - Materials from Ann Friedman (Box-folder 21/12)
      Note card from Ann Friedman to Jocelyn Arem, plus photos and printed copies of photos of Caffè Lena, including Lena Spencer. Also includes a photocopied humorous drawing of Lena cleaning up the stage after a musical performance. Images are in black and white and in color.
    - Jackie Alper, circa 1970s-2000s (Box-folder 21/13)
      Three photos of Jackie Alper, two in color, and one of these with an unidentified woman.
  - Subseries 2: Publicity photos, circa 1970s-1990s
    The majority of photos measure 8 in. x 10 in.
    - Publicity photos "A" (Box-folder 22/1)
      Black and white photos; some have multiple copies.
    - Publicity photos "B" (Box-folder 22/2)
      See note for folder 23/1.
    - Publicity photos "C" (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Publicity photos "D-F" (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Publicity photos "G" (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Publicity photos "H, J-L" (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Publicity photos "M-N, P" (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Publicity photos "R" (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Publicity photos "S" (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Publicity photos "T-W" (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Publicity photos - unidentified performers (Box-folder 22/11)
  - Subseries 3: Photos by Joe Alper, early to mid-1960s
    Black and white prints (each image measures 2 3/4 in. x 1 3/4 in.) of digitized images, usually with 10 images per sheet. Images are watermarked with Alper's name. The list of individuals, groups, and venues given below is not exhaustive.
    - 00di07, rolls 1-2, 11, 16-18, 20-21, early to mid-1960s (Box-folder 23/1)
      Bob Dylan, Suze Rotolo, Lena Spencer, George Alper, Jackie Alper, Guy McKenzie
    - Rolls 126, 129-130, 132-134, 136, 138, 143-145, 152 (Box-folder 23/2)
      Jackie Washington, Sue Abel, Jackie Alper, George Alper, Sylvia Mars, Tom Paley, Lena Spencer, Jaye Alper, Lena Spencer, Pete Stampfel, Jeri Alper
    - Rolls 277, 285-288, 290-291, 297-299 (Box-folder 23/3)
      Molly Scott, Roy Berkley, Dave Van Ronk, Bill Spencer, Lena Spencer, Barry Kornfeld
    - Rolls 309, 315, 321-329, 341, 344-348 (Box-folder 23/4)
      Ramblin' Jack Elliot, Hedy West, Peter La Farge, Mira Gilbert, Rev. Gary Davis, Lena Spencer, Molly Scott, Mark Spoelstra, John Herald
    - Rolls 354, 356-357, 365-366, 370-375 (Box-folder 23/5)
      Jackie Washington, Hedy West, Dave Van Ronk, Caffè Lena Theater, George Alper, Jackie Alper.
    - Rolls 409, 411-413, 424-428, 443-447, 464, 468, 475, 479 (Box-folder 23/6)
      Caffè Lena Theater, Molly Scott, Skidmore Theater, Gil Turner, Noel [Paul] Stookey [Paul Stookey], New Voices Group, Hedy West, Henry Hood, Music Barn, The Weavers
    - Rolls 521, 594-595 (Box-folder 23/7)
      Tom Paxton, Greenbriar Boys
    - Rolls 654, 675 (Box-folder 23/8)
      Gerde's Folk City, John Lee Hooker, Mike Settle, George Alper, Pete Seeger
    - Rolls 740, 794 (Box-folder 23/9)
      John Herald, Ralph Rinzler, Bernice Johnson Reagon, Rutha Harris, Charles Neblett, Freedom Singers, George Alper, Joe Alper
    - Rolls 956, 993-995 (Box-folder 24/1)
      Bernice Johnson Reagon, Charles Neblett, Rutha Harris, Cordell Reagon, Freedom Singers, George Alper, Joe Alper
    - Roll 1075 (Box-folder 24/2)
      Bernice Johnson Reagon, Cordell Reagon, Lena Spencer, Eric Nussbaum, Margaret Cunningham, George Alper
    - Rolls 1149-1151, 1190-1193, 1196-1197, 1199 (Box-folder 24/3)
      Lena Spencer, Jim Kweskin, George Alper, Jeri Alper, Guy McKenzie, Bob Beers, Evelyn Beers, Martha Beers, Jaye Alper, Joe Alper, Hedy West, Ken and Joanie Jenkins, Jane Tillema
    - Rolls 1220-1229, 1233, 1235-1236 (Box-folder 24/4)
      John Hammond, Jr., Larry Older, George Alper, Angus Godwin
    - Rolls 1237-1241, 1247, 1250-1253, 1299 (Box-folder 24/5)
      Angus Godwin, Ed McCurdy, Len Chandler, Clarence (Tom) Ashley, George Alper, Paul Clayton, Rev. Gary Davis, Caroline Paton, Sandy Paton
    - Rolls 1300, 1381-1386, 1390-1393 (Box-folder 24/6)
      Carline Paton, Sandy Paton, Big Joe Williams, John (Short Stuff) Macon, Jackie Alper, Janet Scott, Sterling Clink, George Alper, Jaye Alper
    - Rolls 1404-1406, 1438-1440 (Box-folder 24/7)
      Gil Robbins, Caffè Lena Theater, Jackie Alper, Bernice Johnson Reagon
    - Rolls 1524-1526, 1559-1563, 1568-1572, 1592-1593 (Box-folder 24/8)
      Bridie O'Donnell, Jacqui McDonald [Jacqui and Bridie], Charlotte Daniels, Pat Webb, Pete Williams, David Marash, Megan Marash, Caffè Lena Theater, George Alper, Bill Hjerpe, Bernice Johnson Reagon, Toshi Reagon
    - Rolls 1645, 1679, 1684-1687, 1692-1694 (Box-folder 25/1)
      Caffè Lena Theater, street scenes, animals, studio portraits.
    - Rolls 1835, 1853, 1857-1858, 1860 (Box-folder 25/2)
      Highway scenes, portraits, Caffè Lena Theater, Lena Spencer, Bob Beers, Evelyn Beers, Cordell Reagon
    - Rolls 1975-1976, 1994 (Box-folder 25/3)
      Mark Spoelstra, Ritchie Havens, Gerde's Folk City, Lena Spencer, Joe Alper, George Dawson
    - Rolls 2166, 2251, 2306, 2379-2381 (Box-folder 25/4)
      Pete Seeger, Tom Paxton, Movement Singers, SNCC, Ali Khan [probably Ali Akbar Khan], Buffy Sainte-Marie, Len Chandler, college [campus images], Greenbriar Boys, George Dawson, Charles O'Hagerty
    - Samples of contact sheets (Box-folder 25/5)
      3 black and white images; Joe Alper, photographer. The images may have been copied from contact sheets.
  - Subseries 4: Photos by other photographers, circa 1960s-2006
    - Photos by Jocelyn Arem, 1999, 2005 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Photos by Doris Armstrong, early to mid 1970s (Box-folder 25/7)
      14 photos, 3 1/2 in. x 3 1/2 in.; all but three are in color. Photo IDs on most images, although some are followed by a question mark: Michael Cooney (?), Molly Scott (?), John Herald, Green Mountain Boys [Greenbriar Boys?], Frank Wakefield, Tom Paxton (?), Pat Webb.
    - Joe Deuel Caffè Lena photo collection, circa 1960s-1970s (Box-folder 25/8)
      A group of photos in various dimensions, both black and white and color, taken by other photographers and gathered together by Joe Deuel. Includes photographic images of Lena Spencer and various performers, as well as exhibit visitors. Most of the photos are of lower quality, with many printed on bond paper. Accompanying the images are a few manuscript items, including a trading card for Christine Lavin, and a miniaturized version of the play "Outward Bound," produced at Caffè Lena Dinner Theater.
    - Photos by Howard Eskin - general (1 of 2), 1998-2005 (Box-folder 25/9)